gofreecredit.com 2005-03-07

# PassionUp.com Privacy Policy

At PassionUp, we take safeguarding your privacy online seriously. PassionUp has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the PassionUp network of sites (and emails) including: PassionUp.com, MyPassionUp.com, OptInDeals, SpecialRewards, FreeGiftOffers, and our partner sites. 

How We Use Data:

PassionUp's registration form requests users to give us contact and profile information (such as your name, email address, postal address, zip code, sex, interests). Some of the requested information is required in order to receive certain PassionUp services; other information is optional. 

Ways we use data:

We use data to send personalized, targeted information to the user in their email messages or on our website; to send targeted advertising and promotions in our opt-in newsletters that allows us to provide our service to the users; to send opt-in email offers about products and services of interest or special deals from our partner sites based on the user's chosen interests; to send confirmation of profile changes; to contact users for feedback and surveys; and to send users news about PassionUp, including greeting card newsletters and updates of new or enhanced services. We never send unsolicited spam to our users.

We have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We protect your information by placing it on a secure portion of the Site and by regularly backing up data, performing consistency checks with independently recorded log files to prevent tampering, and restricting access to information on our servers via several user authentication technologies. While it is our goal to safeguard personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you submit such information at your own risk and absolve us of any liability. While we do take steps to limit them, our systems, like all computers, are susceptible to "hackers" and others who illegally seek and gain access to information stored on the computers' hard drives and other memory storage devices. 

I.P. Addresses/Operating System/Browser Type:

When you visit PassionUp.com or click on one of our links, we may automatically record your I.P. address, operating system, and browser version. We use this information to generate usage statistics and to ensure that our site and emails are accessible to the widest possible audience. We may also use I.P. addresses to track abuse of our system and for system administration, diagnostic analysis, site tracking and reporting of aggregate usage information. 

Third-Party Links:

This site (and our emails) contain links to other sites. PassionUp is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other Web sites.

Disclosure of Data:

We request demographic information:

(1. ) To tailor our subscribers' PassionUp experience. With this information we can provide our users with content we think they might be interested in. We believe we will be able to provide users with a better service if demographic information is provided.

(2.) We collect certain information from you in order to process your order. We require your name, address, zip code, social security number, date of birth, email address, and credit card information. We may transfer, sell, or use the information we collect from you to third parties (with the exception of credit card and social security numbers) for the purpose of targeted marketing opportunities.

(3.) We will divulge your private information if required to do so by law and/or to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud and situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person.

Furthermore, we may provide your personal information to the police or other investigating agencies to assist them in the investigation of any suspected violations of law. We also have the right to share your name and contact information with our attorneys in the event of serious violations of conduct.

If served with a subpoena, search warrant, or court order, we would be compelled to provide the required information. We may or may not provide you with the existence of the subpoena, search warrant or court order, or with advance notice of our compliance.

(4.) We do track certain general usage pattern information. This information is used in aggregate form (mass information to show trends and patterns) to improve the Site. Certain information is requested so that we may provide you with targeted advertising. With targeted advertising, we deliver advertising messages to the types of audience's advertisers most want to reach. We use the personal information that you provide to assist in the identification of individuals who meet these criteria. 

Children 13 or Under:

In general, PassionUp.com is a general interest/audience site and is not directed at children under the age of 13. It is PassionUp.com's policy to refrain from knowingly collecting personally identifying information from children 13 or under and to actively discourage children from providing such information at points of collection.

To the extent that PassionUp ever becomes directed at children 13 or under and knowingly collects personally identifying information from those children (such as full name, home address, email address, telephone number or any other information that would allow someone to identify or contact the child) it is PassionUp.com's policy to include parental notice and/or consent features consistent with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. In short, and depending on the nature and intended use of the information at issue, if we ever collect personally identifying information from children, we will provide parental notice or obtain verifiable parental consent as follows: in the case of notice, we will send an email to the parents or legal guardian of the child that informs them i) what information was collected, ii) what contact has been, and/or will be made, and iii) notify the parent that they may request deletion of such information and cessation of any contact; OR, in the case of consent, we inform parents or a legal guardian i) that we wish to collect personal information from the child, ii) that a parent's or legal guardian's verifiable consent is required for the collection, use and disclosure of the information, and iii) how the parent can provide consent.

A parent or legal guardian has the option to agree to the collection and use of the child's information without consenting to the disclosure of the information to third parties. We will send a new notice and request for consent to parents and legal guardians if there are material changes in the collection, use or disclosure practices to which the parent or legal guardian had previously agreed.

At any time, a parent or legal guardian may revoke his/her consent or refuse to allow us further use of his/her child's personal information and request that we delete the information. Effecting such a request can be accomplished using the contact information provided on PassionUp.com. Please note that PassionUp may terminate any service provided to the child if the deleted information at issue is reasonably necessary for the child's participation in that activity.

Sharing/Co-registrations:

During the registration process, subscribers may be asked if they would like to have their registration information made available to companies and partner sites that wish to offer products and services that our subscribers may be interested in. By opting in to receive email offers about products and services of interest, you are granting us permission to combine your personal information with other information, such as prior purchase history and publicly available demographic data, to provide you with email and postal offers geared towards your individual tastes and preferences, and to offer you stand alone advertising emails and third party advertising. We will never share your information with third parties unless you grant us permission to do so.

Referral Program:

As part of our "Send this page to a friend" program, we ask you to provide information (like the name and e-mail address) of your friends and family whom you would like to send a card. Users receive card pick up notification e-mails, but do not become members of PassionUp until they confirm their interest in our service and sign up to receive our newsletter or special offers.

Links:

When we provide you with links in our emails, they may include a special tracking code unique to you which allows us to determine which content and advertisements are most popular.

Cookies:

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. The first time a user provides an email address to PassionUp.com, we put a cookie on the user's PC so that when the user returns to PassionUp.com, using the same PC, PassionUp.com will be able to personalize the user's experience by providing special features, such as keeping track of the user's PassionUp address book for sending greetings, making special offers and other forms easier to fill out. If, at any time, a user provides other information in connection with their activities on PassionUp.com (such as name, address, birth date, gender, etc. in connection with, e.g., entering a contest, completing a survey, or signing up for a promotional offer from PassionUp.com or third-party advertisers), PassionUp.com may store that information, along with the user's email address, in its user database.

PassionUp.com only uses the information stored in its database (i) for the purpose for which the information was originally provided by a user, (ii) to pre-populate information fields in the event a user wishes to sign up for and/or subscribe to services, promotions or offers in the future, (iii) to ensure that a user will not be repeatedly exposed to the same ads, offers and promotions while visiting PassionUp, and (iv) in connection with delivering content, information or newsletters which the user regularly receives from PassionUp or other chosen offers from us or our partner sites.

PassionUp.com does not require users to enable the use of cookies on their browsers in order to access the site and participate in any of the activities offered to users. In addition, a user may, at any time, request that PassionUp.com remove any and all information about a user stored in PassionUp.com's database.

We will never use cookies to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. 

Unsubscribe:

You may unsubscribe from our services at any time. To unsubscribe from our content publications, please email: [email@passionup.com](mailto:email@passionup.com)

Notification of Changes:

PassionUp reserves the right to modify this privacy policy. For this reason, you should regularly check our policy.

Contacting the Web Site:

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:

Customer Service:
